Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 11, folder: 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Technique sof Public Relations The Precinct System, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
    By Harold Brayman. September 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Modern Manager, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
    By Henry B. du Pont. April 28. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Public Opinion, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
    By Harold Brayman. September 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: New Responsibilities For Business Leadership, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
    By Crawford H. Greenewalt. September 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Du Pont Company and its Products, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Chemists, Chemicals and Progress, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
    By David H. Dawson. April 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: The Du Pont Company - History, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Du Pont Research, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Box: 11, folder: 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Contributory Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Thrift Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Your benefits at Du Pont, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Group Accident and Health Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Disability Wage Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
    March 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Du Pont Pension and Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Special Benefits Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Industrial Relations Plans and Practices, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Your Benefits The Extra Plus of Working With Du Pont, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Service Pin Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Employee Benefits Plans and Practices, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: This concerns You, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: you get far more than pay when you work with Du Pont, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Important News For You About Hospital-Surgical Coverage, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Hospital-Surgical Coverage, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Salary Allotment Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Vacation Plan For Wage Roll Employes, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Pension and Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: The Du Pont Thrift Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Industrial Relations Plans, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: E.I. Du Pont De Nemours & Company Committee on Education Aid, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
    January 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: News Release, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
    January 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Constitution and By-Laws of the Belle Works Employees Activities Association, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
    December 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Belle Works Employees Activities Association By-Laws, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: News Release, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
    December 16. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, folder: 3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Du Pont Magazine, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
    September-October. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Maintenance Division Safety Manual, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: the Safe Worker at Elchem, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Office Safety Engineering Department, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Manual of Safe Practices and Information for Employees, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: the Big Word, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
    January-April. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: the Big Word, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
    January-August. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: the Big Word, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
    September. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: the Big Word, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: the Big Word, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: the Big Word, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Safety Information and Instructions for Contractors, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: "Safety is a State of Mind", Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
    By Emile F. Du Pont. April 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Safe Worker, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Safe Worker, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Power Division Safety Manual, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Mental Distraction, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Safety begins here, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Safety Color Code, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Safety and Fire Protection Reference Guide For Supervision, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: The Story of Safety, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Box: 11, folder: 4 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Moonbeams, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: News/Views, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Context, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Box: 11, folder: 5 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Application For Employment, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Employee Relations Department Functional Organization Department, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Du Pont Qualification Record, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Louviers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Organization Chart, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Industrial Relations Plans, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Working with Du Pont, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Salary Allotment Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Organization Chart Employee Relations Department, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
    March 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: EngineeringProjects and People, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Personnel Interview Report, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: You and design division, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: edeaa, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Industrial Relations Plans and Practices, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Lay-Off Notice Plan For Wage Roll Employees, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Continuity of Service Rules, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Experience, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: Business Administration and Liberal Arts Graduatesat Du Pont, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 19: Vacation Plan For Wage Roll Employees, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Box: 11, folder: 6 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Employees' Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    March 11. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, folder: 7 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Faculty and Staff Benefits, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Faculty Handbook, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Personnel Handbook, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Box: 11, folder: 8 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Duke University Regional Center For the Study of Aging, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Box: 11, folder: 9 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Handbook of the Partnership Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Box: 11, folder: 10 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Employment Policies and Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Box: 11, folder: 11 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Your Confidential Personal Security Account for 1954, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Box: 11, folder: 12 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The East River and You, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Box: 11, folder: 13 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Your Idea Bank, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Box: 11, folder: 14 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Your Future, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Your Group Hospital Surgical and Hospital-Medical Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Your Anniversary Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: 20 Questions & Answers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Box: 11, folder: 15 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Noteworthy facts and helpful rules, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: How Kodak People are Selected, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Basica Rules Regulations and Safety Suggestions, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Worker Ideas: Hidden Assets An Intimate Message From New York, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
    By Harry C. Kenney. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, folder: 16 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: General Information For Employees, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Box: 11, folder: 17 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Petroleum, Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Petroleum, Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Box: 11, folder: 18 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Agreement of May, 1936, Washington, D.C., Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Railroad Industry Deciison of Arbitrator, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: President's Board Views firemen-Carrier Dispute, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Vacation Agreement, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
    December 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: President's Board Views Firement-Carrier Dispute, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: The Issues Before The Emergency Board and The Closing Argument For The Carriers in The Engineers and Trainmen's 1946 Rules Clase, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Vacation Agreement, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Vacation Agreement, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Agreement of May, 1936, Washington, D.C., Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: Agreement of May, 1936, Washington, D.C., Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: Non-Ops, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
    August 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Memorandum of Agreement, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
    October 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Non-Ops, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
    December 21. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Vacation Agreement, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 15: Non-Ops, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 16: Agreement and Memorandum, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 17: Meidation Agreement, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 18: Agreement of May, 1936, Washington, D.C., Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 19: Agreement of May, 1936, Washington, D.C., Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 20: Agreement of May, 1936, Washington, D.C., Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Box: 11, folder: 19 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Copy of agreement relating to payments to "The Travelers Insurance Company", Publication (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Box: 11, folder: 20 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Facts Vs. Fallacies On Railroad Bargaining, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Box: 11, folder: 21 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Kodak Highlights, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Kodak Highlights, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Kodakery, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Kodakery, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
    July 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Kodakery, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
    January 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Kodakery, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Kodak Office Suggestion Investigation Form, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: Your SuggestionIt Won't Be The First, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: Find A Better Way, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 10: Kodak Face the Urban crisis A Report, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 11: History of the Eastman Kodak Company, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 12: Eastman Kodak Companya brief history, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 13: George Eastman, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
    By O. N. Solbert. November. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Reporting Business Expenses on Tax Returns, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
    October 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Roll Coating 2nd Open House, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 16: Employes' Guide Book, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 17: When Business Gets Involved, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 18: Applied Photography, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 19: Applied Photography, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 20: Student Tours at Eastman Kodak Company, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 21: Welcome to Kodak, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 22: what's your suggestion?, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 23: What's Your Suggestion?, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 24: What's Your Suggestions?, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 25: What's Your Suggestion?, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 26: What's You8r Suggestion?, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 27: How you are paid, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 28: Applied Photography, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 29: Management Letter, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
    January 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Kodak's Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 31: Eastman Kodak Company, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 32: Eastman Kodak Company, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
    October 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Brief History of the Eastman Kodak Company, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 34: Eastman Kodak Company Today and Tomorrow, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
    By William S. Vaughn. October 16. Item is in English.
- Box: 12, folder: 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Kodak Office, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: the Square Deal, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: how you are Paid, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Hello There, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Your Annual Vacation, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The Square Deal, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: The Kodak Park Works, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Eastman Kodak's Apparatus and Optical Division, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Application for Position as Salesman or Technical Representative, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Kodak Park Athletic Association Recreation Programs, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Personal Qualification Record, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Careers with Kodak, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Box: 12, folder: 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Form A, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Form B, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Box: 12, folder: 3 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A Survey of Motion Picture, Still Photography, and Graphic Arts Instruction, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    By Dr. C. William Horrell. Item is in English.
- Box: 12, folder: 4 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Your Safety Is Worth Working For, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Your Safety Is Worth Working For, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Box: 12, folder: 5 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Box: 12, folder: 6 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Square Deal, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Kodak's "Open Door" Policy, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
    By Craig P. Cochrane. November 27-28. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Kodak's Industrial Relations Objectives and Where We Stand, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
    By C. P. Cochrane. October 27-28. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Kodak's "Open Door" Policy, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Kodak's Industrial Relations Objectives And Where We Stand, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Box: 12, folder: 7 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Kodak Milestones, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Eastman Kodak Companya brief history, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: About Kodak, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: How Kodak Got Its Name, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Biography of George Eastman, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: A brief history of Kodak, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: about Kodak, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Kodak Park Its Products and People, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Story of the Kodak Camera, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Kodak Milestones, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: How Photographic Film Is Made, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Kodak Milestones, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: How Kodak People Are Selected, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Distribution Careers At Kodak, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Photography In Your Future, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Kodak Materials for Visual-Communication Education and Training, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Box: 12, folder: 8 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Industrial Relations Program of Eastman Kodak Company, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: How You Personally Are Sharing In Kodak Plans During 1949, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Kodak's Sickness Allowance Plan For Those Employed In California, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Information for Retired Kidak Men and Women, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: For Immediate Release, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    September 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: When you retire, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Kodak's Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: You and the years ahead, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Eastman Chemical Product's Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Blue Cross Hospital Blue Shield Surgical Protection for The People of Eastman Kodak Company, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Greater insurance protection, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: To Protect Your Health, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: If You Should Become Disabled, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: The Eastman Savings and Loan Association, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Protection for Your Family, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Eastman Kodak Company Eastman Kodak Employees' Savings and Investment Plan, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Major Mediacl Expense Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: when you are Sick, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: when you Retire, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: Educational Aid Program, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 21: Investaccounts, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    August 28. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Educational Aid Program, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 23: Investaccount Payroll Deduction Authorization Card, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 24: Eastman Kodak Company A Picture of Progress 1938-1968, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 25: Business Reply Mail, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 26: A Management Approach To Problems of Individual Adjustment, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    By Allen B. Gates, N. David Hubbell. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Your Wage Dividend, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Box: 12, folder: 9 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Daiy Absence Record, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Record of Employment, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Box: 12, folder: 10 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: H. Paul Nelligan, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    By H. Paul Nelligan. Item is in English.
- Box: 12, folder: 11 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: the "Coin Your Ideas" plan, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Progress Review: Engineer-Industrial, Methods, Process, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Progress Review: Foreman-Machine Repair & Maintenance, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Progress Review: Foreman-Material Handling, Service, etc., Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Axle News, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Axle News, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Axle News, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
    August/September. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Axle News, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Axle News, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Axle News, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Axle News, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Box: 12, folder: 12 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Outline of Industrial Relations Services, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Box: 12, folder: 13 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Joint Consultation in The E.B. Eddy Company, Publication (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Box: 12, folder: 14 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: You and Your Job, Publication (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Box: 12, folder: 15 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: your Ecusta retirement plan, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Box: 12, folder: 16 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: New Measures of Productivity For Manufacturing Industry, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    By Allen W. Rucker. October 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Rucker Plan A New Approach to Higher Productivity and Improved Labor Cooperation, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Economic Productivity-The New Growth Factor in Employee Pay Plans, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    By Allen W. Rucker. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Visitors Day Address, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    By Allen W. Rucker. September 28. Item is in English.
- Box: 12, folder: 17 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: take a lookat the outlook, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Questions and AnswersAbout the Electric Utility Industry, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Box: 12, folder: 18 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Edison Guide Book, Publication (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Box: 12, folder: 19 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Those Who Have Come Our WayWe're Happy They Came Our Way, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Box: 12, folder: 20 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Products of the Electric Auto-Lite Company, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Box: 12, folder: 21 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Cooperative Retirement Income Plan, Publication (Box 12, Folder 21)
    November 23. Item is in English.
- Box: 12, folder: 22 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Amendment to Agreement Between Electric Boat Company and the Marine Draftsmen's Association of the Port of New London, Publication (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Electric Boat Company and Marine Draftsmen's Association of the Port of New London, Publication (Box 12, Folder 22)
    January 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Agreement Between Electric Boat Company and Shipbuilders and Marine Engineers Union of Groton, Connecticut, Incorporated, Publication (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Box: 12, folder: 23 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Health and Welfare Benefits For Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Box: 12, folder: 24 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Exide Management Manual, Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
    January 3. Item is in English.
- Box: 12, folder: 25 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Exide Personnel Inventory, Publication (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Box: 12, folder: 26 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Agreement Between Elgin Division Chicago Rawhide Manufacturing Company, Publication (Box 12, Folder 26)
    July 17. Item is in English.
- Box: 12, folder: 27 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Rules Governing Employes Covered by Agreement With Shop Crafts Committee System Federation NO. 88, Publication (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Box: 12, folder: 28 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Elgin National Watch Company's Pension Fund, Publication (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Elgin Employees' Handbook, Publication (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Agreement Between Elgin National Watch Company and Elgin National Watch Workers Union, Publication (Box 12, Folder 28)